Elephant is a documentary, family, adventure film directed by Mark Linfield.
Disneynature’s Elephant follows African elephant Shani and her spirited son Jomo as their
herd make an epic journey hundreds of miles across the vast Kalahari Desert.
Led by their great matriarch, Gaia, the family faces brutal heat, dwindling resources and persistent
predators, as they follow in their ancestors’ footsteps on a quest to reach a lush, green paradise.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Meghan, Duchess of Sussex.
Elephant is a 2020 American nature documentary film about elephants directed by Mark
Linfield and Vanessa Berlowitz and narrated by Meghan, Duchess of Sussex.
It is the fifteenth nature documentary to be
released under the Disneynature label.
The film was released alongside Dolphin Reef as a
Disney+ exclusive on April 3, 2020.
It received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of elephant, wildlife,
kalahari, nature documentary, baby elephant.
The tone is dark.